Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1929-1995 and undated
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group A, ca. 1961-1995 and undated
    - O'Donnell, Patrick (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - O'Gorman, Ned (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - O'Grady, Desmond (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - O'Hara, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Olivar, Madire (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Olson, Charles (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Olsen, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Olsen, Eric (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Olson, Paul (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Olsen, Tillie (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Omwake, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - O'Neill, Joanna (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - O'Neill, Kevin (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Osborn, Carolyn (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Overall, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Owen, Guy (2) (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Owens, Sue (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Packard, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - PacPerson, Bettijane (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Paine, Lewis (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Palmer, Bryan (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Parish, Mike (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Parker, Boyce Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Parker, Lois M. (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Parker, Wyman (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pasco, Cauny (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Paton, Jack, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pawlowski, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Payne, Betsy P. (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Payne, Ginnie (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Peck, Dick (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Peck, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Peden, William, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Peet, Mary Ann (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pelletier, Gaston (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Penick, Douglas (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pennybacker, Ruth (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Percival, Percy (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pesta, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Peterson, Mary (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Peterson, Jim (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pettis, Maggie (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pettit, Molly (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pevear, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Philbrick, Johanne (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Philips, Jim (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Piercy, Marge (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Pitchford, Kenneth (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Platt, Eugene (Box Alpha. Corr. A8)
    - Plumly, Hope (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Plumly, Stanley (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Poliakoff, Cindy (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Pollard, Joyce (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ponder, Dulane (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ponder, Leanne (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Porter, Mrs. Arabel. J. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Porter, Norman (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Porterfield, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Portis, Rowe, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Posner, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Poster, Carol, (3 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Powers, Pamela (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Powell, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Prager, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Preston, Daniel (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Price, Phyllis (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Price, Reynolds (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Pruden, Mrs. Roy D. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Prunty, Wyatt (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Purviance, Donald (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Palmer -- Puteo (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Quasimodo, Salvatore (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Quigley, Austin (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ragan, Sam (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Raiziss, Sonia (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ramsey, Paul, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ramsey, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Randall, Julia, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ransom, John Crowe (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rappold, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rath, Roger (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ratliff, V.K. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ravetch, Irving (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ravenel, Shannon (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ray, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ray, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Real, Jere (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reddick, Pat and Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reed, Kit, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reed, Mark (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rees, Ennis (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reich, Dave (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reiter, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Remis, Ralph (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Renner, Bruce (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reynolds, Cedric S. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Reynolds, Max (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rhodes, Byno (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rhodes, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ricci, Julio (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ritter, Lucy C. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ritalin, Thane (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roberts, Laurence (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Robbins, Martin (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Robinson, Ann (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Robinson, Bill (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rodenbeck, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roe, Connie (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roetzel, Larry (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rogers, Viola (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rollinson, Phil (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rooke, Leon (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Root, William Pitt, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Root, Judith (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roper, Mrs. George C. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rose, Charles (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roseliep, Raymond, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rosen, Kenneth, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rosenbaum, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rosenfeld, Irene (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rospigliosi, Princess Margherita (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ross, Dan (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ross, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ross, Jean (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rossberg, Stephen (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roth, George L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Roth, Philip (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rovit, Earl (Bud) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ruark, Gib, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rubin, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rubin, Larry, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rubin, Louis, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ruffin, Paul (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rudnicki, Larry (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ruefle, Mary (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ruffin, Paul (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rulon-Miller, Elizabeth (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Ryan, Rick (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Rybaker, Lucille (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - R (Misc.) (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sadoff, Ira (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Saltz, Bob (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sanchez, Sonia (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sanders, Scott (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sandnes, Don (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sandy, Stephen (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sapperstein, Michael (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sarton, May (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Savage, Catherine (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schaible, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schelling, Mrs. H.M. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schevill, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schoenberger, Nancy (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schohart, Art (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Scholes, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schönholzer, Annemarie (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schultz, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schulz, Gretchen (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Schutt, Christine (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Scott, Carolynne (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Scott, Nathan (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Scott, Susan R. (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sears, Cathy (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Sears, Stan (Box Alpha. Corr. A9)
    - Seay, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Secrest, Mrs. Meryle (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Seebring, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Segal, Lore (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Semmler, Mrs. R. A. (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Semsibar, Judith (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Seper, Warren (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Settle, Mary Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Seward, William, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shackleford, Rudy (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shaffer, Stephen Mayo (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shannon, Edgar (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shapard, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sharp, Rhod (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sharpless, F. Parvin (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sharpless, Geoff (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sheldon, Tim (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shelton, Lois (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shelnutt, Eve (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sheppard, Patricia (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shereff, Dorothy (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sherwood, Dolly (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Short, Carvel G. (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Short, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shugrue, Michael (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Shumway, Mary (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sibley, Fred (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Siegel, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Silver, Kelly (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simms, Peg (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simmons, J. Edgar (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simon, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simon, Rose (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simpson, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simpson, Louis (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Simpson, Michael (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sinclair, Bennie Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Singer, Ron (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Skinnner, Knute (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sklarew, Myra (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Slavitt, David, (8 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Slavitt, Lynn (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Slocum, Meg (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Barry (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Ben (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Bob (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Dave (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Ed (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Gerda (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Glenn (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, Stephen E. (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Smith, William Jay (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Snipes, Wilson (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Snodgrass, W.D. (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Snow, Wilbert (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sopko, Jack (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sobehack, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sorel, Julian (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sorenson, Dale (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sorrells, Helen (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sorrells, Bob (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Southall, Deire (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Spackman, Peter (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Spacks, Barry (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Sparks, Larry (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Spears, Monroe K. (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Spier, Jacquelyn (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Spingarn, Lawrence (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Spireng, Matthew (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Squires, Radcliffe (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Staley, Eric (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Standiford, Les (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Stanford, Frank (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Standley, Fred (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Stanton, Maura (Box Alpha. Corr. A10)
    - Starbuck, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Steedman, C. Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Steele, Max (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Steele, Paul (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stegner, Wallace (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stein, Edward (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Steinke, Darcey (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stephens, Martha (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stern, Dan (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stevens, Holly, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stevenson, John W. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stillwell, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Starr, Bill (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stocker, Arthur (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stokes, Michael A. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stokesbury, Leon (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stone, Ed (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stone, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stone, Nancy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stone, Naomi (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stone, Ruth (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stott, Michael J. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stout, Rex (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stovall, Floyd (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Strachan, Bill (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Strand, Mark (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Strater, Mary P. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stuart, Dabney (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Stuit, Dewey (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Styron, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Sullivan, Chester (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Sullivan, Nancy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Sullivan, Peggy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Sullivan, Walter (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Summers, Hollis (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Sverdling, Alex (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Swan, Gladys (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Swann, Brian (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Swann, Roberta (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Sward, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Swiggart, Peter (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Symons, Julian (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Szathmary, Arthur (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Szogy, Alex (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Santos-Steinman (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tagliabue, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tambimuttu (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tannen, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tanner, Douglas (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taormina, Chuck (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Targan, Barry (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tate, Allen (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taubman, Howard (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taylor, Frank (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taylor, Henry (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taylor, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taylor, Julie (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taylor, Peter (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Taylor, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tebb, Barry (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Teltscher, Devborah (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tenshist, Brast (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Terrana, Phil (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Theroux, Alexander (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thomas, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thomas, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thompson, Evelyn (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thompson, Francis (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thompson, Jack (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thompson, Larry (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thon, Melanie (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thorne, Evelyn (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thornton, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Thorp, Willard (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tichmeneff-Troyer, Mrs, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tifft, Ellen (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Timko, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tipkis, Jeff (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tobey, Claire (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Todd, Ruthven (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Todd, Theodora (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tomasino, Luis (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tomek, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Trusky, A. Thomas (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tucker, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tucker, Mrs. V. C. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Tucker, Wayne (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Turco, Lewis (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Turner, Kermit (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Turner, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Twain, Norman (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Twiss, Dorothy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Ullman, Leslie (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Untermeyer, Louis (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Updike, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Urbach, Rosalind (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Urdang, Constance (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vale, Eugene (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vance, Nina (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vance, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - VanderMolen, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vandersee, Chuck (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Van Duyn, Mona (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Van Woerkom, Dorothy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vas Dias, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vaughan, Dick (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vaughan, Sam, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Veeder, Rex L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Venn George (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vest, Quentin (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vinson, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Virgilio, Nicholas (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vodrey, W. H. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vogan, Sara (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Voigt, Ellen Bryant (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Voigt, Milton (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vonnegut, Kurt (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vos, Alvin (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Vowles, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wagenheim, Jack (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wagenheim, Mike (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Waggoner, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wagner, Linda (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Waldau, Roy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walker, David (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walker, Liz (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wall, Donald (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wallace, Bruce (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wallace, Connie (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wallace, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wallace, Wesley H. (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Waller, Harcourt (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walley, Deborah (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walsh, Chad (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walter, Eugene (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walton, Kathy (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Walton, Kathy & Assoc, Writing Program, (3 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Wardlaw, Frank (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Ware, Cade (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Warner, Anne (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Warren, Barbara (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Warren, Leland (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Washington, Mary (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Watson, Nubra (Box Alpha. Corr. A11)
    - Watson, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wearstler, Harriet (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weaver, Gordon (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Webber, Edith D. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Webber, Howard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weeks, Ramona (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weams, J. Edward, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weem, Ben (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weil, Wendy (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weinfield, Henry (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weingarten, Roger (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weir, Howard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weiseman, Jack (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Weiss, Theodore (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Welsh, John R. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Welt, Elly (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wentworth, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Werth, Wyatt (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wescott, Glenway (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - West, John Foster (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - West, Theodora (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Whalen, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wheeler, John P. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wheeler, L. Ray (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wheeler, Sue (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wheeler, Wolcott (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wheelock, John H., (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Whisnant, Charleen (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Christine (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Dottie (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Ellington (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Helen (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Lourine (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Milton (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - White, Jon Manchip (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Whitehead, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Whitehill, Ben (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Whitman, Ruth (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Whitney, Elizabeth (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wier, Allen (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wier, Dara (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wier, Stuart (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilbur, Ellen (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilbur, Frederick (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilbur, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilcox, Maurice (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wild, Bill (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wild, Patricia (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilder, Isabel (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wiley, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilkins, Eithne (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilkinson, Sylvia (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Aubrey (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Clyde (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, D. V. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, J. David (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Jonathan (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Millar (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Polly (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Robert V. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Williams, Thomas (2) (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Willig, Charles (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Willingham, Calder (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Willis, B. Folsom (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Willis, Julia (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilner, Herbert (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilson, Austin (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilson, Clyde (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilson, Robert L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wilson, Siddy (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Windham, Sally (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Winn, Ralph (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Winton, Calhoun (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wingate, Jane (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wise, Hope (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wise, Kelly (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wiseman, Jack (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Witte, Philip (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wittner, Karen (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wochler, Lillian (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wolfe, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wolfe, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wolfstyn, Ron (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wolitzer, Hilma (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wonham, Ann (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wood, Gil (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wood, Paul (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wood, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wood, Susan Thumm (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wood, Thomas G. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Woodbridge, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wouk, Herman (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wright, Bill (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wright, Carolyne (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wright, Charles (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wright, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wright, Stuart (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wright, Ted (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wyatt, Wyatt (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wylie, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Wyndham, Sally (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - W (Misc.) (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Yarbrough, Steve (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Yates, Jamie (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Yates, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Yoken, Mel B. (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Young, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zacharias, Jerrold (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zacharias, Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zehner, Harry (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zelden, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Ziegfield, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zimmer, Paul (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zinnes, Harriet (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zucha, Lisa Trow (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zucker, Jack (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
    - Zuckerman, Phil (Box Alpha. Corr. A12)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group B, ca. 1957-1989 and undated
    Chiefly contains letters to Garrett from representatives and members of organizations, presses, publications, and institutions. Arranged alphabetically by name of institution.
    - Above Ground Press (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Academy of American Poets (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Academy of Television Arts and Science (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Agni Review (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Allen and Company (W.H.) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - American Academy in Rome (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - American Council for Arts in Education (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - American Film Institute (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - American Library Assoc. ( American Libraries ) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Antaeus ( The Ecco Press ) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Anthony Sheil Associates (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Appleton-Century-Crofts (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Apple-Wood Press (Phil Zuckerman) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Approach (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Approaches (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Ashley-Steiner, Inc. (Herb Jaffe) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)
    - Atheneum (Chanles Corn) (Box Alpha. Corr. B1)